Good morning everyone, good afternoon, good evening, my name is Yasumoriwaka, and today I will be answering 100 questions.
If you watch this video, you will know who I am at once! I'm looking forward to it! I'll do my best!
Yes, um, my name is Yasumori-Waka. I am from Fukushima prefecture. My member color is yellow.
My nickname is Wakabayashi.
My birthday is October 30, 2002.
What are you doing when the world is here?
I'm meeting my family and loved ones.
Yukitori, what do you want?
Cartilage.
Do you prefer Yukitori with sauce or salt? Or salt?
I prefer sauce.
I'll take a white lamb with mandarin oranges.
Awkward!
What is your favorite hairstyle?
A bun.
I don't like spicy food.
I want to go gray.
I believe you.
I believe in dying.
I believe it very much.
My personal No. 1 rice accompaniment is fried chicken
Cold kinu, the real thing is kinu
How many ramen noodles can you buy?
Eh, I've never tried it.
I think it's about 2 or 3
I don't know.
What do you need for an expedition?
What's essential?
Uh... that... that...
A charger for your phone.
Which instrument would you play in a band?
Guitar.
I peel and eat baked potatoes.
I do.
What did you dream about recently?
I dreamed that I had a fight with my mother.I dreamed that I had a fight with my mom.
What is your favorite season?
Summer.
I'm a rice person.
Rice, definitely rice.
Ramen noodles taste like... um... salt! Salt.
What is this? Lifetime free transportation is a door to anywhere. A.Sushi. Q.If you could have a conversation, what would it be? A.I like it as it is.
Q.Can you change the name of the group? A.I would definitely like to keep it as it is.
Q.What is your favorite word?
Travel in Japan
Nagano
Overseas
Maldives
On your day off
Let's go out...
I go out with friends.
If it doesn't work out, I sleep in.
A day or two? Recently.
What's your favorite animal?
Capybara!
Kapikapi.
Favorite lyrics and song?
My favorite lyrics are by Ratwings
Favorite song?
I can't pick one!
Let's see...
Wake me up?
Billionaire Girl, or...
I like all of them.
I can't decide.
Favorite English word.
What's this?
My favorite English word.
Strong.Strong.
I don't have a license.
I can run 50m.
I used to run in 7 seconds when I was a student.
I don't know now.
What subject are you good at? Japanese.
Not Pitomitsiri.
What's your favorite subject?
What's my boom these days?
What is it?
Well... Internet shopping.
If you could write one kanji character that describes you...
Let's see... Strong.
The highest and lowest voice you can make
Oh no... My habit is to touch my hair
My favorite TOKUSA song is "Boss
What do you think about during a live performance?
Well, I'm thinking about my
I'm looking for someone to do my...
I'm thinking...
I'm looking all the way to the back to make sure I'm not losing my mind.
I look all the way to the back.
What's your favorite song to sing live?
I wonder... what's the most fun song to sing live?
Maybe "Youth School Trip" or something like that.
Pillow toss
What's your favorite potstickers?
I wonder.
Hmmm...
Uh, potstickers.
Let's see what's in it.
Tofu
My favorite oden ingredient is
Let's see...
Oh, I can't find the name.Oh, I can't find the name.
Satsuma-age
Who do you admire?
People who admire him.
I admire a lot.
Yojiro Noda.
Yes, Mr. Yojiro Noda.
If you could take one thing with you to a deserted island, what would it be? If I could take one thing with me to a deserted island, it would be Yojiro Noda.
If you could take one thing with you to a deserted island, what would it be?
A cell phone.
No, you're lying.
Wait, if I could take just one thing to a deserted island, I wouldn't want to survive on a deserted island.
If I could only take one thing per person, what would it be?
Eh, something that's good at hunting or something.
Who would you take with you to a deserted island?
Who would you take?
Yuna.
Who will replace the member?
Pearl
If you were a man, who would you switch with to be with a member? Pearl! If you were a man, which member would you want to date?
Pearl!
What sport would you like to play?
A sport you'd like to play?
You mean you've never done it before? Not until now.
What's that?
What's that? What's a sport you've never played?
Boxing, that kind of thing, that's a sport.
But I don't want to be in pain. That's fencing. It's the best dance moves in the world.
I'll never get fat.
Two episodes?
Two episodes! Yasubori! YASUBORI Ha!
What song do you recommend for episode 2?
Let's see... I wonder...
Hmmm...
Let's see...
The song we can't loseSongs to Lose
What time do you get up?
Wow.
You're all over the place. Wow.
It varies... if it's an uneventful day or something.
But I definitely get up in the morning.
I get up around 11:00.
And then I go to bed.
I go to bed around 12:00 or 1:00.
When I go to bed, I wear clothes or pajamas.
Pajamas
If I live, I live in the countryside
Member Color
Blue
Most expensive purchase ever
I wonder what it is
What did I buy?
Recently
I bought an AirPots Pro.
What was your biggest fear? My biggest fear...
What's your biggest fear?
What was your biggest fear?
Well, I think it would be... going to Shinspo for Tork's YouTube project.
What is your favorite onigiri ingredient?
My favorite onigiri ingredient is kelp!
What would you like to do in show business?
What kind of entertainment job would you like to do?
ComedianComedianFavorite performing arts job.
Geisha
I take the time of the watermelon first.
Did you believe in anything when you were a child? When I was little, I believed in...
Oh, that dough... I really believed that the dough of Momotaro was that migratory bird when my neighbor's brother told me, but I never stopped writing about it.
I'm about 40 years old.
I want to die. What were you like when you were little? I was naughty!
I'm not 40 at all.
Water or tea? Tea? Water!Water? Tea? Water!
What if you could produce a lot of music?
Well, I'd like to make a snappy dance song with no lyrics in the chorus.
Like EDM.
The karaoke box is, um, Koresawa's cigarettes. Kolesawa cigarettes.
What do you do over New Year's Eve? This year I held hands with my sister and jumped!
Squash time, please!
What do you do on the move? I play games on my phone.
What do you always order when you see a movie?
Caramel popcorn.
What club do you play in?
Basketball team.
I play a lot of difficult songs.
Does that include dancing and singing?
Dancing and singing.
Including dancing and singing.
Dance, sing, dance, sing, dance, sing, dance, sing, dance, sing, dance, sing, dance, sing, dance, sing, dance, sing, dance, sing, dance, sing, sing
I wonder if that includes dancing and singing?
Taai!
I am Metahammer!
Metahammer.
I joined the ambulance service because I was scouted.
I believe in fate.
What was your favorite YouTube star?
I used to love salmon roe.
But I can't eat it anymore.
I eat too much.
What's your favorite thing about yourself?
I'm the type of person who takes good care of people who like me.
If you tell me you like me...
I'll take care of it forever.
What are your hobbies? If you tell me you like me, I'll cherish it forever.
What are your hobbies?
I don't know if I'll confess.I don't know if I'll confess, but...
I don't know.
I'm a good swimmer. I studied swimming my whole life.
The place I'd like to go with the Inari Corps is Okinawa.
Please take me there.
I prefer Western food.
I would like to do a live rice concert at a real estate agency.
If you were to describe your animal side, how would you describe yourself?
Ummm...
Well, I don't know about this.
I like capybaras, but people often say I look like a cat.
I don't know.
What happened to each member? Lun-chan is a white rabbit, a white rabbit with floppy ears.
And Rine is a cat, a black cat, and Yuna is...
Yuna Yuna?
Yuna is a
Tiger
Myself is
Pearl must be a pearl.
Pearl must be
Lis
Karen is the
I wonder if she is Karen.
I wonder if she's a cat.
Is he a cat? He looks like a cat, too.
Mon-chan is a bear and Miyu is a panda.
Kaaya is a...
Uh... Lion.
In a word, the reason for Lion Talk is simple: it's cute!
Each one of us has different tastes and personalities.
But when there are 9 of us, we don't fall apart, we become stronger!
Singers you'd like to have a face-off with
Singer you would like to have an interview with
If it's not a singer but a comedian, it would be Mr. Chokopura.
The part-time job I would like to do is a crepe shop.
Q. What is your favorite candy?Q.What is your favorite candy?
I'm having a hard time deciding what my favorite candy is.
I wonder what it is.
My favorite candy
NAKACAN
Q.What is your favorite part?
What do you like about everyone?
I like you when you like us.
What do you want everyone to fix?
I don't have any. No, I don't. Thank you for everything.
What is the one thing you can say to everyone?
I love you!
What is your ultimate goal as Tohoku-san? Well, I am aiming for Budokan now,
But Budokan is not the ultimate goal,
But it is not the final goal, but to go beyond the Budokan,
I think it is your dream to go beyond the Budokan,
I think that is your goal to continue to be Tohoku-san.
Last but not least!
Lastly, a word of love to the members of Tohoku-san! I think our goal is to keep on doing things in the distance.
Last! Lastly, a word of love to the members of Distant Field!
Thank you for always being with such a young guy.
Let's keep up the good work!
I have successfully completed 100 questions! Thank you so much!
I'm not sure if it's true or not.
I don't know if it's true or not.
but this is the kind of person Yasumoriwaka is.
Thank you very much!
Bye bye! Bye!